<resources>
    <string name="app_name">STDeacons</string>
    <string name="splash_logo_text">Go near an art piece!</string>
    <string-array name="beacon_spinner_array">
        <item>Choose...</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="ok_btn">OK</string>
    <string name="add_btn">ADD</string>
    <string name="loc_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="loc_place">Place:</string>
    <string name="info_subtitle">Museum Companion App</string>
    <string name="info_information">STDeacons is a companion application of
        Group 2 for the interactive art installation which is a partial
        fulfillment for HUME10. The art installation tackles Adolescent
        Sexual Health and various Sexually Transmitted Diseases.</string>
    <string name="info_footer">A Special Project application implementing indoor
        localization using BLE Beacons.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_art_piece">ArtPieceActivity</string>
    <string name="subject_name_holder">Subject n</string>
    <string name="sub1_name_holder">Description</string>
    <string name="sub2_name_holder">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="sub3_name_holder">Treatment</string>
    <string name="large_text1">
        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text2">
        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text3">
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
    </string>
</resources>
