<resources>
    <string name="app_name">STDeacons</string>
    <string name="splash_logo_text">Go near an art piece!</string>
    <string-array name="beacon_spinner_array">
        <item>Choose...</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="ok_btn">OK</string>
    <string name="add_btn">ADD</string>
    <string name="loc_name">Name:</string>
    <string name="loc_place">Place:</string>
    <string name="info_subtitle">Museum Companion App</string>
    <string name="info_information">STDeacons is a companion application of
        Group 2 for the interactive art installation which is a partial
        fulfillment for HUME10. The art installation tackles Adolescent
        Sexual Health and various Sexually Transmitted Diseases.</string>
    <string name="info_footer">A Special Project application implementing indoor
        localization using BLE Beacons.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_art_piece">ArtPieceActivity</string>
    <string name="subject_name_holder">Subject n</string>
    <string name="sub1_name_holder">Description</string>
    <string name="sub2_name_holder">Symptoms</string>
    <string name="sub3_name_holder">Treatment</string>
    <string name="large_text1">
        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text2">
        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="large_text3">
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
    </string>


    <string name="syphilis_information">
        "Modes of Transmission: (via sore or infected blood)\n"
        "\t1. Contact with ulcer during sex (vaginal, penile, oral, anal)\n"
        "\t2. Touching infectious ulcer and it breaks\n"
        "\t3. Transfusion with infected blood\n"
        "\t4. Maternal fetal transmission\n"
        "\t5. Contaminated needles"
    </string>
    <string name="syphilis_symptoms">
        "Primary Stage - hard round painless sore or ulcer at genitalia, mouth or elsewhere within 12 weeks. Heals without scar (infectious ulcer).\n\nSecondary Stage - latent (flu-like symptoms with rashes) which disappear and reappear but there is no bacteria. (infectious blood)\n\nTertiary Stage - spread to major organs especially brain -> insanity and death (non-infectious but progressive, irreversible damage).\n\nPregnancy - may cause miscarriage or congenital birth defects.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="syphilis_treatment">
        "Diagnosis: easy and inexpensive through Venereal Disease Research Laboratory (VDRL) test.\n\nCurable with antibiotics (only in primary and secondary stage). No cure in tertiary stage.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="gw_information">
        "Other name: Venereal Wart\n\nCause: A virus called Human Papilloma Virus (HPV)\n"
    </string>
    <string name="gw_symptoms">
        "Modes of Transmission: highly contagious\n\t * Sexual (common) - initimate skin to skin contact during sex\n\t * Non-sexual (uncommon) - sharing infected towels or clothing\n\nSymptoms: Painless cauliflower-like growths in skin around genitalia, mouth, or inside the vagina/cervix.\n"
    </string>
    <string name="gw_treatment">
        "It is easily curable, but complications might lead to Cancer of the cervix. The only prevention for this is a vervical cancer vaccine which is already discovered and available.\n"
    </string>

    <string name="vd_information">
        "Fun Fact: Trichomoniasis is also called \"trich\".\n\nCauses:\n\t * Bacterial Vaginitis - harmful vaginal bacteria\n\t * Yeast Vaginitis - fungus (yeast)\n\t * Trichomoniasis - swimming protozoa (a one cell animal)\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="vd_symptoms">
        "Modes of Transmissions:\n\t * Bacterial Vaginitis - vaginal contact (sexual means, uncommon mode), overgrowth of harmful bacteria in the vagina due to frequent douching and irrational antibiotic use which also kills friendly bacteria (non-sexual means, common mode)\n\n\t * Yeast Vaginitis - vaginal contact (uncommon mode), overgrowth of fungus in the vagina due excessive antibiotic use (common mode), and immediate sharing of underwear/towels of an infected person with discharge (rare)\n\n\t * Trichomoniasis - almost always sexually transmitted, rarely thru contact of contaminated personal effects or toilet seats\n\n\n"
        "Symptoms:\n\t * Bacterial Vaginitis - vagina have foul-smelling odor plus discharge (Women), inflammation of foreskin, glans penis, urethral opening (Men)\n\n\t * Yeast Vaginitis - 'White-cheese'-like discharge and vulval itchiness (Women), itching and burning sensation on urination; reddening of penis (Men)\n\n\t * Trichomoniasis - vulval itchiness, foul-smelling odor and yellowish-green discharge (Women), no visible symptoms as they are carriers only (Men)\n\n
    </string>
    <string name="vd_treatment">
        "Both types of Vaginitis are easily treatable by antibiotics, creams, suppositories, or oral medicines. Some medicines for yeast infections are available without a prescription. Trichomoniasis is treated with oral medication.\n\n"
    </string>
</resources>
